Fight?
It's serious, right?
First prize is 20,000 yen.
It's true, I get it now.
See, it looks smaller that way.
Yeah, it does.
Exactly, once you go all out, yeah.
Minimum how many people?
30 people are lost. Wait, me? Huh, that, uh, a little that?
Ah, can’t count that many, can’t count that many. Less than I can count with both hands.
This is bad, I’m about to take this off.
The sound is starting.
..
I can't hear it.
I’ll go too, what do you think?
It’s Quair. Now, fully victorious, what do you think?
Huh, I can’t cheat now.
Hurry up here.
Yes.
Thank you so much for really wanting to join.
Lucky.
It’s too heavy first thing.
It’s lower than the video and this, it’s different from earlier.
Get in.
It might go in. Yeah, technically it’s in.
Will it fit? Yeah, huh?
Ah, it will fit, it will.
Yeah.
Okay, it went in.
Easily.
It’s not easy, tell me at least. Embarrassing, quite a bit.
Tight.
This.
It’s tight.
It’s really in. Ah.
Yikes, ah.
Something's happening. Yeah, it feels good.
Embarrassing.
It’s bad, right? Well, no.
It’s big.
Feels good maybe.
Got in once, but the angle’s different, can I do it? Wait a sec.
And, it’s big, this. Yeah, I know. Yeah, it’s really tough, really tough.
Got it.
It’s okay, it went in all at once. All at once.
It went in!
Huh, it’s embarrassing. Watch out, watch out, watch out.
It’s bad, it’s really intense.
Yeah, it’s in. It’s all the way inside. Amazing, I did my best.
I get it, amazing.
Because, I think mine is harder.
This body is amazing.
This really is hard. Yeah, it’s really hard, huh? How do I angle it in? Super hard.
Hard. Will it go in?
Uh, I think it’s connected.
Ah.
It’s really going in all at once. Yeah, it normally does.
It slips right in. Truly, truly.
It’s going in. Is no one moving? No one’s moving?
Wait, really waiting. Wait, huh, no one is moving.
Someone’s going to move. The hips, who is moving? Is it just my imagination?
Yikes.
One person.
If one person moves, everyone, wow, really doing a lot of exercise. Just a bit.
This is bad, someone’s moving too violently. I definitely heard that. Glad I know what’s happening. Wait.
Scary, scary, scary.
Yeah, well, that’s it.
We’ll do it later.
You can leave in order after the salt is gone.
The last person left, that’s not fair.
I don’t want to give up, but it’s impossible now. Waiting outside, seriously.
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry. That’s really intense, sorry, sorry.
Move.
Yes.
Haha.
Ah, it feels so good.
Yeah, yeah.
Ah, no way, it’s okay.
Yeah...
..
Wait, wait, this is bad, this is bad.
Ah, it’s too good, this feels so good.
Oh.
Yikes, wait a second.
Ah, this is bad, so bad. It hurts, hurts.
Hold on, hold on.
Ah, it feels good.
Oh, they’re doing it, doing it. Looking so much.
Yeah, this is bad.
No, no, stop, stop, stop. This is bad, this is bad.
No.
Loading a lot. So thick. It came out a lot. And you’re touching and got some.
Feeling good now. Wash this off and it’ll be okay. Can wash it off. Someone’s a real pro, so they can handle it.
Maybe.
It gets really better. When it’s inside.
What should I say? It’s our secret, see?
Should I give this to you? Please move aside. I did it. Can we continue? That, it’s big. This is the prize money, and if you want to keep going with sex, I’ll give it. Not millions, no, I’ll do it. I’ll do it, yeah.
Wow, it’s big. Happy? Not happy.
This?
Yes, yes, be quiet.
Can I touch? Is it okay to touch? Is it alright? It’s a bit white.
Wow, nice. It’s Riko, right?
Like, I feel good when I’m being touched. Embarrassing.
..
My type is different, seeing this.
Nipples hard.
Nipples, this damn thing, ejaculated inside. Nipples trembling.
Getting excited.
Huh, loud voice. Sperm is coming out so much, this is bad, bad.
Yikes, yikes, yikes.
So bad.
Yikes, yikes yikes yikes yikes yikes yikes.
Incredible, no, no, no.
Ah, it’s bad, it’s really bad. Wait, it feels way too good..
..! Ah, it’s bad. I came a little. Let’s try hard.
Wait, wait, wait. No, it’s no good. It’s really bad.
..
Can you shout loudly and hold my face? Are you holding it?
Wow, so intense.
Ah..
..
Hehe..
Can I put my mouth in too?
Yeah, sure.
..?
I was able to move it in and out a lot.
Should I go all the way inside? Okay?
..
Can I cross over a little?
First time here.
Can I try to insert?
Yes.
I’ll put it in.
Aaaaah.
Haha.
Nananaha.
Ah..
..
....
Are you okay?
We’re fine.
..
Can I reach further forward with my hand?
Can I get closer?
Yes, let’s go.
Okay.
Yikes...
What’s happening? Yes.
..
Hmm...
And.
Can you kneel?
..
Ah...
Yikes, yikes. Yikes...
Yikes, yikes, yikes.
..
Her face looks happy when her pussy is inside his penis. Can I see closer?
...
Wow. Why? Why is it so amazing? Because it feels so good.
Ah, no, stop. No, stop.
Ah, yikes. It’s bad, yikes.
Yikes, yikes.
Ah.
Ugh, ah.
Yeah, it seems like it might come out somewhere.
..
Ah..
I might come too.
..
I came.
Thank you very much. Money. Oh, those red ones like mom’s panties. Here it is. That’s panties.
This.